realtystore.com 2019-07-14

# RealtyStore.com: Homes for less. More for you.

**Privacy Statement:**  
We have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of the data gathering and dissemination practices applicable to our web site (Site). By visiting, registering or using services obtained through our Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with any terms of this Policy, please do not use or submit any personal information to this Site.

 **RealtyStore.com Privacy Pledge:**  
We do not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer, and we are the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We fully disclose our privacy policy in this document. If you have any questions or comments, you are invited to contact us.

 **Information We Collect:**  
We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you register to use this Site; when you use, participate or purchase products and services through this Site; and when you ask to be provided additional services. The type of personal information that we collect may include full name, email, telephone number, address, payment information, profession, company name, company website address, business telephone number and photo. This personal information is generally required if you wish to enroll or participate in our services. We may use, sell or distribute certain individual personal information to other companies, including related interests or vendors so as to provide you with important offers. We may keep all information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy indefinitely. When you register for the RealtyStore.com Professional Network ("REP"), certain information you post or share with third parties, such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, or other information, will be shared with or accessible by other users who have access to the Network. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please be aware that we may amend this policy at our sole discretion. You can check back to view changes at anytime by visiting the Site www.RealtyStore.com and clicking on the privacy link at the bottom of the page.

 **Disclosure of Your Information:**  
We will not rent or sell your mobile telephone number to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may use or disclose such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We need to enforce our Terms of Use.
  * We provide such information to a company controlled by, or under common control with, RealtyStore for any purpose permitted by this Policy.  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share Personal Information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of RealtyStore’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer Personal Information about you if RealtyStore is, or its assets are, acquired by or merged with another company.

 **Personally Identifiable Information:**  
Personally Identifiable Information refers to any information that can be used to identify you as an individual in any way. Enrollment in any RealtyStore.com service is contingent upon your agreeing to the Terms and Conditions of membership and providing Personally Identifiable Information as described above.

 **Anti-SPAM Policy:**  
The RealtyStore.com marketing program has a strict policy regarding unsolicited email. Because email is an integral part of our services, your signup ensures that you'll receive information relative to your interests at the time of your enrollment from RealtyStore.com. If you later wish to cease participation in this portion of our services, you may do so at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link or button found within such message. Please note that opting not to receive email does not exempt you from receiving administrative and informational emails from us, which include but are not limited to, notices about membership status changes and alterations to our Terms.

 **Aggregate Data:**  
We may, from time to time, contact you regarding opportunities that may be of interest to you. In that process, we may use a third party service provider to manage our database and communication system in order to send that correspondence to you on our behalf. If you respond to a communication to take advantage of an offer you may see or receive, you share your Personally Identifiable Information with a third party. From time to time, we do share non-personally identifiable information collected in aggregate, anonymous form with third parties so that they may better evaluate what products and services are most appealing to different segments of our member base.

 **Automatically Collected Information:**  
When you log on to our Site, our server may automatically recognize you by an encrypted member key, also referred to as a "cookie." This cookie acts as a unique identifier. We may use third party cookies and clear pixels (also referred to as "web beacons") to measure page views and email responses. These devices allow us to identify unique visitors to our Site and act as a counter for ongoing monitoring of Site, email and corresponding future transaction activity related to a specific offer.

 **Third-Party Websites and Services:**  
We are not responsible or liable for the content or data practices of any third-party site, including those of our advertisers, affiliates, partners, or vendors. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of all third-party sites carefully before sharing your Personally Identifiable Information with them. Occasionally, you may be offered the opportunity to participate in an offer or service that, by its very terms, will require us to forward your Personally Identifiable Information to the advertiser or partner so that they can provide the service to you. As always, it is your choice to participate. We do not guarantee the content or information practices of any third-party site. You alone are responsible for determining the appropriateness of sharing your Personally Identifiable Information with our advertisers. We have your consent to share collected personally identifiable information (including email addresses) with third parties for commercial purposes, such as advertising.

 **Communication:**  
We are available to you during normal business hours to answer any privacy-related questions or concerns you might have. Simply contact us and we will respond in a timely manner. You sign up for our marketing program when you submit the information on the first page of our sign-up process, and our marketing partners or we may contact you via email with offers we think you will like. We have a strict Anti-SPAM policy, and you may unsubscribe at any time while still participating in our services. We do not collect or use any information about you for marketing purposes, except for information that you have provided to us or authorize us to obtain, or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make our programs and services more relevant to your interests.

 **Security:**  
RealtyStore.com has established company-wide security policies and practices designed to protect your and others information from unauthorized intrusion. These practices include, but are not limited to, firewall security, the use of appropriate encryption technology, and the use of multiple levels of password security. All RealtyStore.com employees are required to familiarize themselves with, and abide by, these safeguards.   However, please note that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

 **A Special Note Regarding Individuals Under 18 Years Old:**  
The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of eighteen (18), and we request that such individuals not provide personal information through the Site. If you are under 18 years of age, you may browse our Site; however, you may not provide personal information to us such as name, address, or email address, and you may not register for, enroll in, and/or make product purchases.

 **Change In Business Operations:**  
Please note that if RealtyStore.com or any lines of its business are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, liquidation, sale of assets or otherwise, its customer database could, in whole or in part, be sold or otherwise transferred to a third party as part of that transaction. There may be instances when we may disclose your information without providing you with a choice in order to protect our legal rights or those of our affiliates, or those of our or our affiliates' employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process.

 **International Visitors:**  
Your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States or any other country where we have facilities, and by providing us with your information, you consent to the transfer, storage and processing of such information outside of your country.

 **Your California Privacy Rights:**  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for those third parties direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by US Mail at 5951 Encina Rd. Suite 208 Goleta, CA 93117 Please include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond.

Thank you for becoming familiar with the RealtyStore.com privacy policy. You can always contact us with any questions.
